Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Records SC0756
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH_1993_131
  - S.U. Bulletin (Box 11)
  - Stanford Album (Box 11)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 11)
  - Stanford Daily - Microfilm Project (Box 11)
  - Stanford Electronics Laboratory (Box 11)
  - Stanford Heritage Video (Box 11)
  - Stanford Historical Society (SHS) Meeting 1982, 1983 (Box 11)
  - SHS Annual Meeting 1983 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Inventory of Plaques (Box 11)
  - SHS - Correspondence (Box 11)
  - SHS - All years, Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - SHS Postcard Project (Box 11)
  - SHS Postcards (Box 11)
  - SHS - Program Committee (Box 11)
  - SHS - talks at meetings (Box 11)
  - SHS - Sacramento House Comm (Box 11)
  - SHS - Membership Lists and Directories (Box 11)
  - SHS - Members 1984 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1975-76 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1976 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1977] (Box 11)
  - SHS - Board Minutes, 1977-78 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1978 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1979 (Box 11)
  - SHS - 1979-80 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1980 (Box 11)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1981 (Box 11)
  - SHS - 1981-82 (Box 11)
  - SHS - 1982 (Box 12)
  - SHS - Minutes and Agenda, 1983, 1984 (Box 12)
  - SHS - Minutes, 1984, 85, (86) (Box 12)
  - SHS - 1986 (Box 12)
  - SHS - 1987 (Box 12)
  - SHS - extra minutes (Box 12)
  - SHS - Newsletter (Box 12)
  - Stanford Instructional Television Network (Box 12)
  - Stanford Library Users Group (SLUG) (Box 12)
  - Stanford Museum -- Stanford Collection (Box 12)
  - Stanford Museum: correspondence (Box 12)
  - Stanford Profiles (Box 12)
  - SRI: correspondence (Box 12)
  - Stanford Sierra Camp (Box 12)
  - Stanford University Press: catalog of books in print (Box 12)
  - Statistics - general (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, July 1, 1977 - June 16, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Statistics (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, 1978-1979 (Box 12)
  - Statistics 1978-79 (Annual Report) (Box 12)
  - Statistics, 1978-79 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, 7/80-12/80 (Box 12)
  - Statistics - 1979-80 (Box 12)
  - Stats (Box 12)
  - Statistics, 1980-81 (Box 12)
  - Statistics, Quarterly (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Statistics 1981-82 (Box 12)
  - Statistics 1982-83/ University Libraries (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, 1982-83 (Summer Quarter) (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, 1982/83 (Fall Quarter) (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Circulation, Sept. - Dec. 1982 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, Winter Quarter 1983 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Circulation, Winter Quarter 1983 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, Spring Quarter 1983 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Reference, Summer Quarter 1983 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Summer Quarter 1983 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Fall Quarter 1983 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Winter Quarter 1984 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Spring Quarter 1984 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Summer Quarter 1984 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Fall Quarter 1984 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Winter Quarter 1985 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Spring Quarter 1985 (Box 12)
  - Statistics -- Summer Quarter 1985 (Box 13)
  - Statistics, 1985-86 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Fall Quarter 1985 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Winter Quarter 1986 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Spring Quarter 1986 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Summer Quarter 1986 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Fall 1986 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Winter 1987 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- Spring 1987 (Box 13)
  - Statistics -- RLIN (Box 13)
  - Student Publications (Box 13)
  - SUA - SC Merger (Box 13)
  - SULA (Box 13)
  - SUL -- Green Library renovation (Box 13)
  - SULSA -- Health Safety Subcommittee (Box 13)
  - SULSA (Box 13)
  - Supervisors Council (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Correspondence (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- expenditures (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- external, information and price lists (Box 13)
  - Supply requests 1980/81 -- Completed (Box 13)
  - Untitled (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Requests Completed 1983-84 (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Requests Completed 1984-85 (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Requests Completed 1985-86 (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Requests Completed 1986-87 (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Requests Completed 1987-88 (Box 13)
  - Supplies -- Requisitions (Box 13)
  - Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues (SWOPSI) (Box 13)
  - Systems Office (Box 13)
  - Talks (Box 13)
  - Tapes, audio (Box 13)
  - Tax Laws (Box 13)
  - Technical Reports (Box 13)
  - Technical Reports -- Correspondence (Box 13)
  - Technical Reports -- Computer Science Dept. Microfiche (Box 13)
  - Technical Reports -- Policies (Box 13)
  - Technical Services Advisory Council (Box 13)
  - Technical Services Group -- Meeting Minutes (Box 13)
  - Technology Center of Silicon Valley (Box 13)
  - Telephones (Box 13)
  - Terminal (Box 13)
  - Terminal - CRT (Box 13)
  - Thefts (Box 13)
  - Theses 1956, 1957 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1958, 1959 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1960, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1962, 1963 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1964 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1965 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1966 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1974 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1975 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1976 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1977 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1978 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1979 (Box 13)
  - Theses 1980 (Box 14)
  - Theses 1981 (Box 14)
  - Theses 1982 (Box 14)
  - Theses -- General (Box 14)
  - Theses -- Missing Cards (Box 14)
  - Theses -- Missing in Archives (Box 14)
  - Theses -- Missing Pages (Box 14)
  - Theses -- Policies re., 1971 (Box 14)
  - Tours and Talks -- Walking Tour (Box 14)
  - Tours and Talks (Box 14)
  - Tours -- Historic Campus (Box 14)
  - Transfers (Box 14)
  - Transfer Items: In Process (Box 14)
  - Transportation to SU (Box 14)
  - Travel Advances (Box 14)
  - Travel Funds (Box 14)
  - Travel Requests (Box 14)
  - Treat, Payson J., Fund (Box 14)
  - Trustees, Board of (Box 14)
  - Turner, Paul (Box 14)
  - Typewriter (Box 14)
  - Undergraduate Historical Soc. (Box 14)
  - University Library Council (Box 14)
  - University of Santa Clara (Box 14)
  - University Seminars (Box 14)
  - Vacations (Box 14)
  - Values, Technology, Science and Society (Box 14)
  - Video Cassette Player (Box 14)
  - Video Disk Programs (Box 14)
  - Video Reproduction (Box 14)
  - Videotapes (Box 14)
  - Videotape - SDI (Box 14)
  - Visiting Committee (Box 14)
  - Visitors (Box 14)
  - Visitors, Information for (Box 14)
  - Visual Art Services (Box 14)
  - Volunteers (Box 14)
  - Water Damage -- Information (Box 14)
  - Water Damage (Box 14)
  - Woman's Heritage Museum (Box 14)
  - Woman's Heritage Museum (Box 14)
  - Word Graphics (Box 14)
  - Word Processing (Box 14)
  - Word Processing -- Library (Box 14)
  - Word Processing Info. (Box 14)
  - Yale University: Mss Archives (Box 14)
- Records, Accession ARCH_1995_021
  - Administrative files, 1959-1976: Annual reports - to - ACRL, Rare Book Section meeting (Box 1)
  - Administrative files, 1953-1976: ACRL, Rare Book Section - to - Exhibit (Napoleon) (Box 2)
  - Administrative files, 1961-1971: Exhibit - to - Exhibitions (Box 3)
  - Administrative files, 1964-1975: Exhibitions, Administration - to - Loans, in and out (Box 4)
  - Administrative files, 1964-1977: Reader services - to - Photocopy record of orders (Box 5)
  - Administrative files, 1953-1975: Photocopy record of orders - to - Student timesheets (Box 6)
- Antiquarian Book Dealers Files, 1984-1989; Accession ARCH_2001_234
  - Dealers, A – G; includes:
    - Bell, Peter (Box 1)
    - Bell, Book Radmall (Box 1)
    - Bennett, Stuart (Box 1)
    - Black Sun Books (Box 1)
    - Blackwell, B. H., Ltd. (Box 1)
    - Brick Row Book Shop (Box 1)
    - Burmester (Box 1)
    - Califia (Box 1)
    - Chiesa, Carlo A. (Box 1)
    - Dailey, William and Victoria (Box 1)
    - Gerits Sons (Box 1)
    - Gilbert, Bennett (Box 1)
    - Grinke, Paul (Box 1)
  - Dealers, H – Mag; includes:
    - Heath, A. R. (Box 2)
    - Hill, Jonathan (Box 2)
    - Howell, John and Warren (Box 2)
    - Howes Bookshop Ltd. (Box 2)
    - In Our Time (Box 2)
    - Joseph the Provider (Sipper, Ralph Bruno) (Box 2)
    - Karmiole, Kenneth (Box 2)
    - Kraus, H. P. (Box 2)
    - McKittrick, Bruce (Box 2)
    - Maggs Bros., Ltd. (Box 2)
  - Dealers, Man – Sh; includes:
    - Mancevice, Jeffrey D. (Box 3)
    - Mott, Howard S. (Box 3)
    - Norman, Jeremy (Box 3)
    - Pickering Chatto, Ltd. (Box 3)
    - Quaritch, Bernard, Ltd. (Box 3)
    - Rogoyski, Alexander (Box 3)
    - Rootenberg, B. L. (Box 3)
    - Rosenthal, Bernard M. (Box 3)
    - Rostenberg, Leona (Box 3)
    - Schreiber, E. K. (Box 3)
    - Serendipity Books (Box 3)
    - Shasky, Florian (Box 3)
  - Dealers, So – Z; includes:
    - Sokol, A. C. (Box 4)
    - Stonehill, C. A. (Box 4)
    - Wreden, Wm. P. (Box 4)
    - Ximenes (Box 4)
- Records, Accession ARCH_2006_075
- Copy negatives for patron reproduction requests, Accession ARCH_2007_270
  - Books: Barchas, Gunst, RBC (with some arrears) (Box 1)
  - Books: Felton, Newton, Healy, Robinson, 71-xxx, Taube Baron, arrears, MLM, Colonial Newspapers, RBCR, bookplates, Antiquarian Maps, Dewey (Box 2)
  - Manuscripts: M0001 – M0361 (Box 2)
  - Manuscripts: M0362 – M1310, accession numbers, MSS Codex, JL, MSS Photo, Misc collections (Box 3)
  - Archives: Albums (call number A) (Box 3)
  - Archives: PC [not 2, 6, 75, 80 or 84], Hatfield Aerials, Prints, Museum Objects, maps, posters, LC-cataloged books, SCM, accession numbers, architectural drawings [only 1, already in digital form], OS negs [includes GP numbers, maps, prints, and miscellaneous], and a few unidentified negatives (probably of GP images) (Box 4)
  - Archives: SC 001 – SC 529; 4digit collection; Quads (Box 5)
- Records, Accession ARCH_2009_215
  - Manual 1955: Introduction; Bender Room (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manual 1955: Felton Library; Hopkins Room (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Manual 1955: Personnel; Printing (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Manual 1955: Robinson collection; Statistics; Theatre Collection; Transportation Collection (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Manual 1955: Typographical; Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Manual 1955: Supplement; Index (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Manual 1955: loose items, including a letter to Terry Bender from Jeannette Hitchcock (compiler of the Manual) 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- University Archives Chronological Files, Accession ARCH_2009_260
  - Nov. 1978-June 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - July 1, 1979-June 30, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - July 1980-June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - April 1981-June 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - July 1982-June 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - July 1982-June 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - July 1984-June 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - July 1985-June 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Exhibits Department Records, 1969-2010; Accession ARCH_2010_056; 32 Linear Feet; (22 boxes)
  - Gilbert White, Oct. 1989 (removed due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gilbert White: Carnochan (1989) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gilbert White: Case Layouts (1989) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gilbert White: Case Maps/Format (1989) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gilbert White: Case 18 Art (1989) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gilbert White: Diorama Cases 19 and 20 (1989) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gilbert White: Cits/annotated (1989) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gilbert White: Citations and Call Numbers (1989) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gilbert White: Caption Blanks -- long text (1989) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gilbert White: Captions and Case Titles (1989) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Gilbert White: Citations and Caption Format (1989) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gilbert White: Correspondence (1989) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Gilbert White: Exhibit Expenses (1989) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gilbert White: Final Text (1989) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gilbert White: Graphics (1989) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gilbert White: Invoices (1989) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gilbert White: Keepsake -- Notes (1989) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gilbert White: Exhibit Notes (1989) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gilbert White: Poster (1989) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gilbert White: Poster Mockups (1989) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gilbert White: Text (1989) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Kafka Exhibit: April, 1990 (Cancelled due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Kafka Exhibit: Keepsake (1990) (Cancelled due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pasternak Exhibit: Sept 29-Oct 21, 1990 (Cancelled due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pasternak Exhibit: 1990 (Cancelled due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Recent Acquisitions: Oct. 1990 (Cancelled due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Recent Acquisitions: Case Maps (1990) (Cancelled due to earthquake) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Yeats/Healy: Call Numbers for Citations (Oct. 1990) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Corrections Made in Paste-up (1990) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Cover Design (1990) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Hon. Mention, RBMS Catalog Awards (1990) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Illustrations (1990) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Layout and Type Specs (1990) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Press Sheet (1990) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Printing Specs (1990) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Yeats/Healy: Catalog -- Rough Proofs (1990) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Yeats/Healy: Correspondence (1990) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Yeats/Healy: Final Proof (1990) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Yeats/Healy: Outdoor Sign (1990) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Yeats/Healy: Pavilion Attendance Records (1990) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Yeats/Healy: Photographs Reproduced for Show from W.B. Yeats and His World (1990) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Yeats/Healy: Publicity (1990) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Yeats/Healy: Supplies and Expenses (1990) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Yeats/Healy: Troubleshooting Notes (1990) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Yeats/Healy: Work Log (1990) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Freud: Jan.-Mar. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Freud: Captions and Citations (1991) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Freud: Case Titles (1991) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Freud: Citations -- rough (1991) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Freud: Mtg. Notes/To Do Lists (1991) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Freud: P.O's and Receipts (1991) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Freud: Poster (1991) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Freud: Publicity (1991) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Freud: Exhibit Sign (1991) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Book of Nature: Feb. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Book of Nature: Feb. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Book of Nature: Bancroft Loan (Feb. 1991) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Founder's Day Exhibit (March 1991) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Founder's Day Exhibit, Case 1 (1991) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Founder's Day Exhibit, Case 2 (1991) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Founder's Day Exhibit, Case 3 (1991) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Founder's Day Exhibit, Case 4 (1991) (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Exhibit (1991) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Exhibit Keepsake (1991) (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr.: Exhibit Sign and Text (1991) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Mysteries Revealed: March 1991 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Mysteries: March 1991 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Mysteries: Expenses (1991) (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Mysteries: Keepsake (1991) (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Mysteries: Publicity (1991) (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Mysteries: Publicity (1991) (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Mysteries: Sample Mounted Text (1991) (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - SUL Centennial: Case Maps (April 1991-October 1991) (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Centennial: Case Texts (1991) (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Centennial: Correspondence (1991) (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Centennial: Catalog Correspondence (May 1991) (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Centennial: Expenses -- Purchases and Receipts (1991) (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Centennial: Items on Loan (1991) (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Centennial: Library Histories and Photos Displayed (1991) (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Centennial: Library Photos (1991) (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Centennial: Poster and Invitation (1991) (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Centennial: Programs and Exhibits (1991) (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Centennial: Publicity (1991) (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Centennial: Sample Mounted Text (1991) (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Centennial: Sign and Banners (1991) (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Centennial: Supplementary Text (1991) (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Centennial: Task Sheets and Timeline (1991) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Centennial: Text and Selections (1991) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Centennial: Word Version (1991) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A Stanford Legacy: Budget (Autumn 1991) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Legacy: Content (1991) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Legacy: Entry Panel (1991) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Legacy: Invitation Distribution (1991) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Legacy: Invitation Revision (1991) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Legacy: Layout (1991) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Legacy: Out Front Sign (1991) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Legacy: Overdoor Stencil (1991) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Legacy: Press Release and Correspondence (1991) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Legacy: Quotes (1991) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Legacy: The Stanford Century proof pages (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Legacy: A Stanford Legacy / Invitation (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Legacy: Titles and Intro Text (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Legacy: Work Logs (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Academic Cornerstone: Sample Mounted Text (Sept. 1991 -- Oct. 1991) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Redmon Collection: Exploring the West (July 1991 -- September 1991) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Redmon: Expenses (1991) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Redmon: Loan List (1991) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Redmon: Text and Citations (1991) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Traditions: Content Notes (June 1991) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Commencement: Keepsake (1991) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Commencement: Keepsake (1991) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kelmscott Press Anniversary: Morris / Berger Collection (Nov. 1991-Jan. 1992) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Kelmscott: Content (1991) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Kelmscott: Correspondence (1991) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Kelmscott: Expenses (1991) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Kelmscott: Keepsake (1991) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Kelmscott: Keepsake Design (1991) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Kelmscott: Keepsake Graphics (1991) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Kelmscott: Publicity and Correspondence (1991) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Kelmscott: Text (1991) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Hand Bookbinding Today: March 1992 -- April 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bookbinding: Acceptance/Rejection Letters (1992) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bookbinding: Books Returned (1992) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bookbinding: Captions (1992) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog (1992) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bookbinding: 1/22 meeting at press re: catalog (1992) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Contents/Text (1992) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Cover Art (1992) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Design (1992) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Distribution (1992) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Correspondence (1992) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Preliminary Designs (1992) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bookbinding: Catalog Title Page (1992) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bookbinding: Entry Forms (1992) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Bookbinding: Exhibit Production Notes (1992) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Bookbinding: George Litho Update (1992) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Bookbinding: Latest Proofs (1992) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Bookbinding: Layout (1992) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Bookbinding: List of Entrants (1992) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Bookbinding: Loan Agreement Forms (1992) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Bookbinding: Opening Invitations (1992) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Bookbinding: Photo Diagrams -- Recto and Verso (1992) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Bookbinding: Price List (1992) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Bookbinding: Publicity (1992) (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Bookbinding: Rejected loan forms/entry forms (1992) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Bookbinding: Return Mail Proc. (1992) (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Bookbinding: Signed Loan Forms (1992) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bookbinding: Signs and Banners (1992) (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Bookbinding: Slides of Books (1992) (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bookbinding: Supplies and Expenses (1992) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Whoosh! Stanford Women's Basketball: Jan. 30-April 15, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Higher Than Most (Clinch, Mountaineering): April -- July 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Clinch: Expenses (1992) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Clinch: Graphics (1992) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clinch: Keepsake Art (1992) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Clinch: Layout (1992) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Clinch: List and Correspondence (1992) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Clinch: Mountaineering Show (1992) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Clinch: Signs and Graphics (1992) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Clinch: Text (1992) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hopkins Centennial: July -- October 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hopkins: Centennial Exhibit (1992) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hopkins: Expenses (1992) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hopkins: Marine Prints (1992) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hopkins: Photos (1992) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hopkins: Publicity (1992) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hopkins: Sign (1992) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Nine Stanford Presidents: October -- December 1992 Intro Text and Background Material (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Presidents: Large Graphics (1992) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Presidents: Postcard (1992) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Presidents: Branner (1992) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Presidents: Casper (1992) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Presidents: Jordan (1992) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Presidents: Kennedy (1992) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Presidents: Lyman (1992) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Presidents: Pitzer (1992) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Presidents: Sterling (1992) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Presidents: Tresidder (1992) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Presidents: Wilbur (1992) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Presidents: Publicity (1992) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Presidents: Receipts and Cost Summary (1992) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Presidents: Sample Mounted Text (1992) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Presidents: Seal (1992) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Presidents: Texts and Citations (1992) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Moderns: The Campbell-White Collection -- Bindery Specs (Jan. -- April 1993) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Moderns: Catalog Final Proof/Specs (1993) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Moderns: Catalog Mailing (1993) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Moderns: Catalog Rough Copy, Edited (1993) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Moderns: Citations, Final (1993) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Moderns: Correspondence and Notes (1993) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Moderns: Cover Designs (1993) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Moderns: Expenses (1993) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Moderns: Fliers -- 2 Versions (1993) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Moderns: Font Possibilities (1993) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Moderns: Keepsakes, 2 each (1993) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Moderns: Layout and Citations (1993) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Moderns: Loan Agreement (1993) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Moderns: Publicity -- Press Release (1993) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Moderns: Samples (1993) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Moderns: Signs (1993) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Moderns: Stencilling Project (1993) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Moderns: Text (edited) (1993) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Holderlin: Philosopher and Poet (April-June 1993) -- Expenses (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Holderlin: Fonts (1993) (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Holderlin: Graphics (1993) (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Holderlin: Layout (1993) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Holderlin: Postcard (1993) (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Holderlin: Publicity and Correspondence (1993) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Holderlin: Sign (1993) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Holderlin: Suggestions and Edits (1993) (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Holderlin: Text -- Rough Copy (1993) (Box 3, Folder 62)